{
    "id": "e9ea6351590e4912991ab7bc17bbe6a6",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don't like ....................... of my physics teachers.",
            "description": "Not either means the same as neither. The sentence given above can also be written as: I like neither of my physics teachers. ",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... people don't trust politicians.",
            "description": "We use most of before a pronoun or a noun with a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither .......................................... the door.",
            "description": "After either and neither we use a singular noun and a singular verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "keys open",
                "key opens",
                "key open"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of .......................................... valid.",
            "description": "After neither of, we use a plural noun and a singular verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "this argument is",
                "these arguments is",
                "these arguments are"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "....................... the shops are closed on Sundays.",
            "description": "We use most before a noun without a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They spend ........................... their income on movies.",
            "description": "We can leave out of after all, both and half. ",
            "answers": [
                "half",
                "half of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. my friends wished me on my birthday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No one of",
                "None of",
                "None"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": ".................. child was given a present.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Each",
                "Each of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. his ideas are quite interesting.",
            "description": "We can leave out 'of' after all when they are followed by nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ my children are engineers.",
            "description": "We can leave out 'of' after both when they are followed by nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Both of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "His ideas are ............................ different from those of his peers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The new job isn't ............................... different from the old one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}